<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:mixinTypes="[rep:AccessControllable]"
    jcr:primaryType="sling:Folder"
    jcr:title="Science Fiction">
    <jcr:content jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
        <folderThumbnail/>
    </jcr:content>
    <thrawnalliances
        cq:commerceType="product"
        cq:tags="[geometrixx-outdoors:activity/biking,geometrixx-outdoors:activity/hiking]"
        jcr:description="Grand Admiral Thrawn and Darth Vader team up against a threat to the Empire in this thrilling novel from bestselling author Timothy Zahn."
        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
        jcr:title="Thrawn: Alliances"
        sling:resourceType="commerce/components/product"
        goodRead="8"
        identifier="photo3"
        noOfPages="368"
        price="100"
        publishedDate="{Date}2018-07-24T00:00:00.000+05:30"
        rating="8"
        starRating="8"
        summary="&lt;p>&lt;b>Ominous words under any circumstances, but all the more so when uttered by Emperor Palpatine. On Batuu, at the edges of the Unknown Regions, a threat to the Empire is taking root--its existence little more than a glimmer, its consequences as yet unknowable. But it is troubling enough to the Imperial leader to warrant investigation by his most powerful agents: ruthless enforcer Lord Darth Vader and brilliant strategist Grand Admiral Thrawn. Fierce rivals for the emperor's favor, and outspoken adversaries on Imperial affairs--including the Death Star project--the formidable pair seem unlikely partners for such a crucial mission. But the Emperor knows it's not the first time Vader and Thrawn have joined forces. And there's more behind his royal command than either man suspects.&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;In what seems like a lifetime ago, General Anakin Skywalker of the Galactic Republic, and Commander Mitth'raw'nuruodo, officer of the Chiss Ascendancy, crossed paths for the first time. One on a desperate personal quest, the other with motives unknown . . . and undisclosed. But facing a gauntlet of dangers on a far-flung world, they forged an uneasy alliance--neither remotely aware of what their futures held in store.&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Now, thrust together once more, they find themselves bound again for the planet where they once fought side by side. There they will be doubly challenged--by a test of their allegiance to the Empire . . . and an enemy that threatens even their combined might. &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
        textIsRich="[true,true]">
        <assets jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <asset
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="commerce/components/product/image"
                assetCategory="[stockphotography:arts_and_entertainme/arts_symbols]"
                fileReference="/content/dam/catalogs/catalog/fiction/science-fiction/36385853.jpg"/>
        </assets>
    </thrawnalliances>
</jcr:root>
